



# **INTRO:**

I'm a B.Sc mechanical engineering student at the Iran University of Science and Technology. I have a keen interest in renewable energy systems. I have some experience in 3D modelling, Drawing, Research and Development, Solar Energy Systems, Hydrogen Production, Waste Recycling Systems and Machine learning. I am highly motivated to learn new things and work hard with others. Additionally, I can share my knowledge to others.

# **EDUCATION:**

# Iran University of Science and Technology

Bachelor Degree of Mechanical Engineering

GPA: 3.80/4.00, Grade: 17.50/20.00

# National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents

Diploma in Mathematics

GPA: 4.00/4.00, Grade: 19.76/20.00

# **SKILLS:**

## **SOLIDWORKS:**

3D modelling, Drawing, Drafting, Simulation, Motion Study

#### **MATLAB:**

Programming, Simulink, Machine learning (ANN Toolbox)

# Ansys:

Turbomachinery, Fluent, Mechanical

## Python:

Programming, Numpy, Pandas, Machine learning (Scikit learn, TensorFlow)

# **PVsyst:**

PV Power Plant Simulation

#### **PVSOL:**

PV Power Plant Simulation

#### **HOMER:**

Renewable Energy system simulation

#### AutoCAD:

Drafting, Construction Drawing, Cutting plan

#### **AVEVA PDMS:**

Piping, Iso draft

## EES:

Thermodynamic analysis

#### **Microsoft Office:**

Word, Excel, Project, Power point

## Sidewinder:

Conveyor designing

### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

# Design Engineer & Piping Engineer

TTS Group - Full Time 2023 - Present

3D modelling of Sari Waste Recycling and Separation, Conveyor Designing for Waste Separation, Piping Engineering for Waste-to-energy power plant of Sari, GD&T, Research and Development

### **Teacher Assistant**

Iran University of Science and Technology - Part time 2022 - 2023
Fluid Mechanic I

### **Research Assistant**

Iran University of Science and Technology - Part time 2022 - Present

Machine learning application for Hydrogen production with Solar energy (Under Submitted)

### Intern

Moshanir Power Engineering Services Co - Part time 2021

Wind Power Generation and Wind Turbine

#### Intern

Manjil Green Power Generation Co - Part time 2020

Wind Power Generation and Wind Turbine

## **RESEARCHES:**

# Weather Forecasting with Machine Learning

Prediction of the next day Temperature and GHI for Tehran & Zahedan with Python

# **Hydrogen Production Simulation**

Simulating PEM Electrolyzer with MATLAB

# **Quality Control for PV Power Plant**

Forecasting the next day Quality of Power Generation for Sama Zahedan PV Power Plant with Python

### **PV Power Plant Simulation**

Simulating Sama Zahedan PV Power Plant with PVsyst

# **CONTACT:**



www.linkedin.com/in/iliya-baktash-626066248



Baktashiliya@gmail.com

